Guide to the Western Filmscript Collection
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- July 2013 Acquisitions, 1941-2007-02-15; 7.58; (7 boxes)
  - Six Feet Under, 2004 (Box 146)
    Television script for Episode 503 "Hold My Hand," written by Nancy Oliver.
  - Six Feet Under, 2005 (Box 146)
    Television script for Episode 504 "Time Flies," written by Craig Wright. Script for Joanna Cassidy.
  - Six Feet Under, 2005 (Box 146)
    Television script for Episode 505 "Eat a Peach," written by Rick Cleveland. Script for Joanna Cassidy.
  - Six Feet Under, 2005-01-24 (Box 146)
  - Six Feet Under, 2005 (Box 146)
    Television script for Episode 506 "The Rainbow of Her Seasons," written by Jill Soloway.
  - Six Feet Under, 2005 (Box 146)
    Television script for Episode 507 "The Silence," written by Bruce Eric Kaplan.
  - Six Feet Under, 2005 (Box 146)
  - Six Feet Under, 2005 (Box 146)
    Television script for Episode 508 "Singing for Our Lives," written by Scott Buck. Script for Joanna Cassidy.
  - Six Feet Under, 2005 (Box 146)
    Television script for Episode 510 "All Alone," written by Kate Robin. Script for Joanna Cassidy. Contains memo on security measures regarding scripts.
  - Six Feet Under, 2005 (Box 146)
    Television script for Episode 510 "All Alone," written by Kate Robin. Contains a call sheet, shooting schedule, and yoga class schedule. Script for Joanna Cassidy.
  - Six Feet Under, 2005 (Box 146)
    Television script for Episode 509 "Ecotone," written by Nancy Oliver. Contains memo on security measures regarding scripts.
  - Six Feet Under, 2002-2006 (Box 146)
    Contains promotional materials, a vehicle pass, a visitor's pass, and shooting schedules.
  - Sky King, 1951-12-12 (Box 150)
    Television script for episode "The Man Who Forgot," written by Joe Richardson.
  - Sky King, 1952-01-14 (Box 150)
    Television script for episode "Formula for Fear," written by Joe Richardson.
  - Sky King, 1952-02-07 (Box 150)
    Television script for episode "One for the Money," written by Joe Richardson.
  - Stories of the Century, 1954-03-25 (Box 149)
    Television script for "Bill Longley," written by Joe Richardson.
  - Stories of the Century, 1954-03-31 (Box 149)
    Television script for "The Doolin Gang," written by Joe Richardson.
  - Stories of the Century, 1954-04-14 (Box 149)
    Television script for episode "Tom Horn," written by Joe Richardson.
  - Stories of the Century, 1954-12-29 (Box 149)
    Television script for episode "Jim Courtright," written by Joe Richardson.
  - Tombstone Territory, 1959-12-14 (Box 149)
    Television script for episode "Lady Killer," written by Joe Richardson.
  - [DUPLICATE - DELETE], 1955-01-26 (Box 150)
    Television script for episode "Journey Into Danger" written by Joe Richardson.
  - Western Marshall, 1955-01-26 (Box 150)
    Television script for episode "Journey Into Danger," written by Joe Richardson.
  - Western Marshall, 1955-01-28 (Box 150)
    Television script for episode "Poison Trail," written by Joe Richardson.
  - Western Marshall, 1955-02-03 (Box 150)
    Television script for episode "Two Men Out," written by Joe Richardson.
  - Wild Bill Hickok, circa 1957 (Box 149)
    Television script for episode "Masquerade at Mocassin Ridge," written by Joe Richardson.
  - Wild Bill Hickok, 1957-08-05 (Box 149)
    Television script for episode "Mail Order Bride," written by Joe Richardson.
  - Wild Bill Hickok, 1957-10-02 (Box 149)
    Television script for episode "Town Without Law," written by Joe Richardson.
  - Wild Bill Hickok, 1957-11-18 (Box 149)
    Television script for "The Counterfeit Ghost," written by Joe Richardson.
- September 2013 Acquisition, 1934-08-20-1996-02-12; 1.75; (3 boxes)
  - The Barbary Coast, 1975-02-28 (Box 152)
  - Barfly, 1986-08-12 (Box 152)
  - The Best Little Whorehouse in Texas, 1981-04-14 (Box 152)
  - Branded, 1965-03-04 (Box 152)
    Television script for episode "The First Kill," written by Frank Chase.
  - Branded, 1965-03-09 (Box 152)
  - Branded, 1965-09-16 (Box 152)
    Television script for episode "10,000 for Durango," written by Jerome B. Thomas.
  - Branded, 1965-09-24 (Box 152)
    Television script for episode "Romany Roundup," written by Jameson Brewer.
  - Branded, 1965-09-24 (Box 152)
  - Branded, 1966-01-26 (Box 152)
    Television script for episode "The Assassins Part One" written by Jameson Brewer.
  - Branded, 1966-01-31 (Box 152)
    Television script for episode "The Assassins Part Two," written by Jameson Brewer.
  - The Cowboys, 1973-12-11 (Box 152)
    Television script for episode "The Rawhiders," written by Jim Byrnes.
  - The Cowboys, 1973-12-26 (Box 152)
    Television script for episode "The Long Rider," written by James Lee Barrett.
  - The Cowboys, 1973-12-31 (Box 152)
    Television script for episode "David Done It," written by James Lee Barrett and John Hawkins.
  - The Cowboys, 1974-01-04 (Box 152)
    Television script for episode "Death on a Fast Horse," written by Ward Hawkins.
  - The Cowboys, 1974-01-04 (Box 152)
    Television script for episode "Requiem for a Lost Son," written by James T. Byrnes and John Hawkins.
  - Dirty Little Billy, 1971-03-11 (Box 152)
  - Inside Moves, 1979-10-12 (Box 152)
  - It's a Gift, 1934-08-20 (Box 152)
  - It's a Mad, Mad, Mad, Mad World, circa 1963 (Box 152)
  - L.A. Confidential, 1996-02-12 (Box 153)
  - The Last Starfighter, 1983-04-08 (Box 152)
  - Mask, 1984-02-22 (Box 152)
  - Mask, 1984-04-05 (Box 152)
  - Mask, 1984-04-19 (Box 152)
  - Mother, Jugs, and Speed, 1975-09-22 (Box 152)
  - [DUPLICATE - DELETE], 1975-09-22 (Box 152)
  - Sanford and Son, 1974-07-24 (Box 154)
    Television script for episode "Ol' Browneyes is Back," written by Rick Mittleman.
  - Sanford and Son, 1975-10-13 (Box 153)
    Television script for episode "The Greatest Show in Watts," written by Jerry Ross.
  - Sanford and Son, 1975-11-07 (Box 154)
    Television script for episode "Lamont in Love," written by Ted Bergman.
  - Sanford and Son, 1976-09-09 (Box 153)
    Television script for episode "California Crude," written by Alan Eisenstock and Larry Mintz.
  - Sanford and Son, 1976-11-13 (Box 154)
    Television script for episode "Here Today, Gone Today," written by Warren S. Murray.
  - Sanford and Son, 1976-11-16 (Box 154)
    Television script for episode "Here Today, Gone Today," written by Warren. S. Murray.
  - Sanford and Son, 1977-01-10 (Box 154)
    Television script for episode "When John Comes Marching Home," written by Alan Eisenstock and Larry Mintz.
  - Sanford and Son, 1977-01-24 (Box 153)
    Television script for episode "Fred the Activist," written by Richard Freiman and Stephen Young.
  - Sanford and Son, 1977-02-02 (Box 153)
  - Sanford and Son, 1977-02-11 (Box 153)
    Television script for episode "Funny, You Don't Look It," written by Joseph Feinstein.
  - Texasville, 1989-08-01 (Box 153)
  - The Train Robbers, circa 1973 (Box 153)
  - Where the Hell's That Gold?!!?, circa 1988 (Box 153)
- October 2013 Acquisition, 1938-12-10-1990-05-14; 2.17; (2 boxes)
  - 1941, 1976-09-21 (Box 155)
  - The Adventures of Red Ryder, circa 1940 (Box 156)
    Contains television scripts for episodes 1-12.
  - The Big Fix, 1977-08-03 (Box 155)
  - The Big Fix, 1977-10-19 (Box 155)
  - Bob & Carol & Ted & Alice, 1968-09-05 (Box 155)
  - Brubaker, 1979-07-19 (Box 155)
  - California Suite, 1978-01 (Box 155)
  - Daughter of Don Q, circa 1945 (Box 156)
  - Hammett, 1979-07-23 (Box 155)
  - Hammett, 1980-01-28 (Box 155)
  - Hammett, 1981-09-06 (Box 155)
  - I Ought to Be in Pictures, 1981-07-15 (Box 155)
  - Inside Daisy Clover, 1965-01-28 (Box 155)
  - Inside Daisy Clover, 1965-02-12 (Box 155)
  - Jerry Saved From Drowning, circa 1985 (Box 155)
    Working title of "Down and Out in Beverly Hills" (1986).
  - The Marrying Man, 1990-05-14 (Box 155)
  - Pink Cadillac, circa 1986-1987 (Box 156)
  - Pink Cadillac, circa 1988 (Box 156)
  - Power to Burn, 1938-12-10 (Box 155)
  - The Sweet Ride, 1967-06-06 (Box 155)
  - Swing Shift, 1982-10-01 (Box 155)
  - Tales of Famous Outlaws, circa 1953 (Box 155)
    Includes episodes 1-11 of television series "Tales of Famous Outlaws," also known under the title "Lash of the West."
  - The Trip to Bountiful, 1985-01-17 (Box 156)
  - Villa Rides, 1967-05-05 (Box 155)
- November 2013 Acquisition, 1972-1977; 0.42; (1 box)
  - Sanford and Son, circa 1972 (Box 157)
    Television script for episode #6 "We Wuz Robbed!," written by Aaron Ruben.
  - Sanford and Son, circa 1972-1977 (Box 157)
- December 2013 Acquisitions, 1960-02-09-1975; 0.83; (2 boxes)
  - Ocean's Eleven, 1960-02-09 (Box 159)
  - One Flew Over the Cuckoo's Nest, circa 1973-1974 (Box 158)
  - One Flew Over the Cuckoo's Nest, 1974-12-05 (Box 158)
  - One Flew Over the Cuckoo's Nest, 1975-12-15 (Box 158)
    Contains combined continuity script.
  - One Flew Over the Cuckoo's Nest, circa 1975 (Box 158)
  - One Flew Over the Cuckoo's Nest, circa 1975 (Box 158)
  - One Flew Over the Cuckoo's Nest, circa 1975 (Box 158)
  - Robin and the 7 Hoods, 1963-10-15 (Box 159)
  - Sergeants 3, 1961-05-10 (Box 159)
    Cover title is "Soldiers 3." Typescript title is "Badlands."
- February 2014 Acquisitions, 1938-04-16-1987-06-09; 1.5; (2 boxes)
  - Big Daddy, 1987-06-09 (Box 161)
  - Bite of the Bullet, 1969-02-25 (Box 160)
  - Cisco Kid #1, 1948-07-02 (Box 160)
    Contains script for "Cisco Kid #1", also called "Valiant Hombre."
  - Colorado Sundown, circa 1951 (Box 160)
  - Dragoon Wells Massacre, circa 1957 (Box 160)
  - This Earth is Mine, circa 1959 (Box 161)
  - The Fast Ones, undated (Box 160)
  - Fate Is the Hunter, 1963-09-30 (Box 160)
  - The Gun Hawk, 1962-11-21 (Box 160)
  - Guns of the Magnificent Seven, 1968-01-29 (Box 160)
  - A Little Spanish Town, 1947-07-21 (Box 160)
  - Malibu (Part Two), 1982-07-16 (Box 160)
  - Malibu (Part One), 1982-07-16 (Box 160)
  - Marshal of Cripple Creek, 1946-10-26 (Box 160)
  - Montana Belle, 1948-10-19 (Box 160)
  - One From the Heart, 1981-01-01 (Box 161)
  - Singing Guns, 1938-04-16 (Box 160)
  - Stagecoach to Hell, 1963-10-22 (Box 160)
  - Texas Terrors, 1940-09-23 (Box 160)
  - Who Shot Roger Rabbit?, 1986-09-02 (Box 161)
    Working title for "Who Framed Roger Rabbit?"
  - Windswept, 1949-04-16 (Box 160)
  - Zoot Suit, 1981-01-02 (Box 161)
- March 2014 Acquisition, 1966-05-1989-08-04; 1.08; (1 box)
  - Body Double, 1982-03 (Box 162)
  - Chico and the Man, 1974-06-27 (Box 162)
    Television script for episode "The Manuel Who Came to Dinner".
  - Chico and the Man, 1974-07-20 (Box 162)
    Television script for episode "No Room in the Garage".
  - Chico and the Man, 1975-11-13 (Box 162)
    Television script for episode "The Dream," written by Ron Friedman.
  - Mackenna's Gold, 1966-05 (Box 162)
  - Mackenna's Gold, 1967-02-09 (Box 162)
  - Postcards from the Edge, 1989-08-04 (Box 162)
  - Sanford and Son, 1974-08-20 (Box 162)
    Television script for episode "The Surprise Party," written by Saul Turteltaub and Bernie Orenstein.
  - True Grit, 1968-08-26 (Box 162)
- July 2015 Acquisitions, 1930-03-27-1993; 6.92; (7 boxes)
  - 100 Rifles, 1967-05-05 (Box 164)
  - Ace Eli and Rodger of the Skies, 1971-03-25 (Box 164)
  - Another Man, Another Woman, circa 1977 (Box 164)
  - Back to the Future, 1984-10-12 (Box 169)
  - The Bank Shot, 1973-09-06 (Box 169)
  - Bad Bascomb, 1944-08-04 (Box 164)
  - The Best Little Whorehouse in Texas, 1981-08-21 (Box 164)
  - Billy the Kid, 1930-03-27 (Box 169)
  - The Blue Gardenia, circa 1953 (Box 169)
  - Bonanza, circa 1940 (Box 164)
  - Canadian Pacific, 1948-07-26 (Box 169)
  - Cat People, 1981-01-15 (Box 169)
  - Chisum and the Lincoln County Cattle War, 1969-05-12 (Box 169)
  - Comes a Horseman Wild and Free, 1977-05-24 (Box 163)
  - Country, 1983-09-13 (Box 164)
  - Dealing: Or the Berkeley - to - Boston Forty Brick Lost-Bag Blues, 1970-08-31 (Box 168)
  - Dealing: Or the Berkeley - to - Boston Forty Brick Lost-Bag Blues, 1970-11-09 (Box 168)
  - Dealing: Or the Berkeley - to - Boston Forty Brick Lost-Bag Blues, 1971-02-09 (Box 168)
  - Death Valley Days, circa 1959 (Box 164)
    Television script for episode "The Talking Wire," written by John Grey and C. Ray Stahl.
  - The Doors, 1990-02 (Box 169)
  - Epitaph for a Gunman, circa 1961 (Box 164)
  - Farewell, My Lovely, circa 1975 (Box 163)
  - The Fargo Phantom, 1949-07-15 (Box 164)
  - Fast-Walking, 1980-05-06 (Box 169)
  - The Girl from Gunsight, 1949-05-13 (Box 164)
  - Gobs and Gals, 1951-11-10 (Box 167)
  - The Godfather Part II, 1973-09-24 (Box 169)
  - Goodbye Charlie, 1964-02-13 (Box 168)
  - The Great Republic of Rough and Ready, circa 1966 (Box 164)
  - The Great Waldo Pepper, 1973-10-31 (Box 169)
  - Guess Who's Coming to Dinner, 1967-02-15 (Box 169)
  - The Gun Fighter, 1949-08-31 (Box 169)
  - Hail Hero, 1969-02-20 (Box 164)
  - Hired Guns, circa 1956 (Box 164)
  - Horn, 1979-01-02 (Box 169)
  - I Love You, Alice B. Toklas!, 1967-10-30 (Box 168)
  - The Invasion of the Bodysnatchers, 1977-12-30 (Box 169)
  - The Iron Star, circa 1963 (Box 164)
    Contains the original treatment for "The Iron Star," later called "The Death of Sitting Bull," an episode of "The Great Adventure television series.
  - Keeper of My Heart, 1968-11-05 (Box 164)
  - La Bamba, 1986-07-21 (Box 169)
  - The Last of the Cowboys, 1976-09-13 (Box 166)
  - Law for Tombstone, 1937 (Box 168)
  - Love in Blume, 1972-07-11 (Box 168)
    Contains filmscript later retitled "Blume in Love."
  - Lucky You, circa 1940s (Box 164)
  - The Mack, 1972 (Box 167)
    Contains final revision script.
  - Mack, 1972 (Box 167)
  - Mel Brooks' Silent Movie, 1975-11-19 (Box 167)
  - Mommie Dearest, circa 1981 (Box 166)
  - My Three Sons, 1969-07-10 (Box 167)
    Contains television script for episode "Who is Sylvia?," written by George Tibbles.
  - My Three Sons, 1970-05-18 (Box 167)
    Contains television script for episode "Four for the Road," written by Bob Touchstone.
  - My Three Sons, 1970-05-25 (Box 167)
    Contains television script for episode "The Elopement," written by George Tibbles.
  - My Three Sons, 1970-05-25 (Box 167)
    Contains television script for episode "The Power of Suggestion," written by Doug Tibbles.
  - My Three Sons, 1970-05-25 (Box 167)
    Contains television script for episode "St. Louis Blues," written by Lois Hire.
  - My Three Sons, 1970-05-28 (Box 167)
    Contains television script for episode "My Four Women," written by Bob Touchstone.
  - My Three Sons, 1970-06-08 (Box 167)
    Contains television script for episode "One by One They Go," written by George Tibbles.
  - My Three Sons, 1970-06-26 (Box 167)
    Contains television script for episode "Robbie's Honey," written by Arthur Sheekman.
  - My Three Sons, 1970-08-06 (Box 167)
    Contains television script for episode "The Bride Went Home," written by George Tibbles.
  - My Three Sons, 1971-05-21 (Box 167)
    Contains television script for episode "Happy Birthday Anyway," written by George Tibbles.
  - My Three Sons, 1971-06-08 (Box 167)
    Contains television script for episode "Katie's Career," written by George Tibbles.
  - My Three Sons, 1971-06-17 (Box 167)
    Contains television script for episode "The Advent of Fergus," written by George Tibbles.
  - My Three Sons, 1971-07-01 (Box 167)
    Contains television script for episode "Whatever Happened to Ernie," written by George Tibbles.
  - My Three Sons, 1971-07-15 (Box 167)
    Contains television script for episode "Buttons and Beaux," written by Joe Connelly.
  - My Three Sons, 1971-07-23 (Box 167)
    Contains television script for episode "Polly's Secret Life," written by Doug Tibbles.
  - My Three Sons, 1971-12-20 (Box 167)
    Contains television script for episode "Special Hour."
  - Nobody Loves a Drunken Indian, 1969-03-26 (Box 164)
  - Nobody Loves Flapping Eagle, 1969-05-16 (Box 164)
  - Paint Your Wagon, 1967-12-01 (Box 164)
  - Pulp Fiction, circa 1993 (Box 166)
    Contains shooting schedule and calendar.
  - Pulp Fiction, circa 1993 (Box 166)
    Contains location list, equipment list, crew list, production board, and the beginning of the Pulp Fiction film script.
  - Pulp Fiction, circa 1993 (Box 166)
    Contains the end of the Pulp Fiction film script.
  - Quien Sabe?, circa 1966 (Box 169)
    Contains treatment for the 1966 film "A Bullet for the General." Italian title: "Quien Sabe."
  - Raising Arizona, circa 1985 (Box 166)
  - Red Sky at Morning, 1970-07-22 (Box 165)
  - Ride the Man Down, 1952-03-11 (Box 167)
  - Run Shadow Run, 1969-03-03 (Box 168)
    Contains filmscript with title crossed out and replaced with "Cover Me Babe," which it was later retitled.
  - The Saga of Jimmy D., A Pony Express Rider - 1860 -, 1976-04-20 (Box 165)
  - Sandflow, 1936 (Box 168)
  - Skidoo, 1968-01-22 (Box 166)
  - Slim Carter, 1957-02-12 (Box 165)
  - Son of the Morning Star, circa 1990 (Box 165)
  - The Strawberry Statement, 1969-08-28 (Box 166)
  - Ten Tall Man, circa 1951 (Box 165)
  - Terminator, 1982-10-20 (Box 167)
  - The Texans Ride, 1941-05-07 (Box 166)
  - They Shoot Horses, Don't They?, 1968-10-29 (Box 167)
    Contains estimating draft.
  - They Shoot Horses, Don't They?, Undated (Box 167)
  - Thundering Caravans, 1952-02-19 (Box 167)
  - The Toughest Man in Tombstone, 1952-03-05 (Box 167)
  - Van Nuys Blvd., circa 1979 (Box 166)
    Contains director's script, cast and crew list, and shooting schedule.
  - The WAC from Walla Walla, 1952-02-06 (Box 167)
  - Wait Till The Sun Shines, Nellie, 1951-01-23 (Box 165)
  - Way of a Gaucho, 1951-01-23 (Box 165)
  - The Way to the Gold, 1956-12-19 (Box 165)
  - Wharf Angel, 1933-12-26 (Box 166)
    Contains screenwriter Frank Partos' script.
  - What's Up, Doc?, 1971-08-01 (Box 166)
  - White Dog, 1981-03-24 (Box 166)
  - Wild in the Country, 1960-09-12 (Box 166)
  - Wild in the Streets, circa 1968 (Box 166)
  - The World in His Arms, 1949-12-13 (Box 165)
- November 2015 Acquisition, 1934-02-01-1993-08-30; 4.33; (4 boxes)
  - 10, 1978-07 (Box 170)
  - 40 Pounds of Trouble, 1962-02-22 (Box 173)
  - Be Cool, circa 2003-2004 (Box 170)
  - California Suite, 1977-11 (Box 172)
  - Chain Reaction, 1982-03-22 (Box 170)
  - The Cheap Detective, 1977-02 (Box 172)
  - The Cheap Detective, 1977-05-16 (Box 172)
  - Choose Me, circa 1984 (Box 171)
  - Coffy, 1972-12-14 (Box 171)
  - Coffy photographs, circa 1973 (Box 171)
    Contains photographs for 1973 film "Coffy."
  - Death Wish II, 1981 (Box 170)
  - Devil in a Blue Dress, circa 1994 (Box 171)
  - Even Cowgirls Get the Blues, 1991-03-07 (Box 170)
  - Everybody's All-American, circa 1987-1988 (Box 173)
  - Fat City, 1970-11-04 (Box 173)
  - Framed, 1973-06-14 (Box 173)
  - Governor's Lady, 1984-07-27 (Box 173)
  - The Graduate, 1967-03-29 (Box 173)
  - Grand Canyon, 1990-12-12 (Box 173)
  - The Grasshopper, 1968-09-05 (Box 171)
  - The Grissom Gang, 1970-04-06 (Box 173)
  - Hardcore, circa 1977 (Box 172)
  - Headin' for Trouble, circa 1948 (Box 172)
    Contains filmscript later titled "Courtin' Trouble."
  - Honolulu, circa 1939 (Box 171)
  - Johnny Angel, 1944-10-21 (Box 171)
  - Little Fauss and Big Halsy, 1968-08-08 (Box 173)
  - Look in Any Window, 1960-07-26 (Box 173)
    Includes cutter's script.
  - Lord Love a Duck, 1965-06-01 (Box 173)
  - Mr. Kool, 1973-02-01 (Box 171)
  - The Music Man, 1960-12-12 (Box 172)
    Includes several shooting schedules and a call sheet.
  - The Music Man, 1961-02-03 (Box 172)
  - Myra Breckinridge, 1968-07-21 (Box 172)
  - Myra Breckinridge, 1969-07-24 (Box 172)
  - Myra Breckinridge, 1969-09-04 (Box 172)
  - Nickelodeon, 1975-09-01 (Box 172)
  - Nickelodeon, 1975-10-08 (Box 172)
  - Old Boyfriends, 1977-11-17 (Box 172)
  - Old Boyfriends, circa 1977 (Box 172)
  - The Other Side of the Mountain, circa 1974 (Box 170)
  - The Other Side of the Mountain Part II, 1977-05-03 (Box 170)
  - Paper Moon, 1972-08-04 (Box 171)
  - Paper Moon, 1972-09-01 (Box 171)
  - Play It as It Lays, 1971-11-24 (Box 173)
  - The Quick and the Dead, 1993-06-24 (Box 173)
  - The Quick and the Dead, 1993-08-30 (Box 173)
  - Rolling Thunder, 1976-04-16 (Box 172)
  - The Shepherd of the Hills, 1940-06-11 (Box 171)
  - Six Weeks, 1981-11-30 (Box 173)
  - Smile, circa 1975 (Box 173)
  - S.O.B., 1979-12 (Box 170)
  - The Sugarland Express, 1972-12-14 (Box 171)
  - They Only Kill Their Masters, 1972-04-10 (Box 173)
  - Triggerman, 1948-03 (Box 172)
  - Truck Turner, 1973-10-29 (Box 171)
  - Valdez Horses, 1970 (Box 173)
  - The Villain, circa 1979 (Box 171)
  - Vision Quest, 1983-09-06 (Box 170)
  - Welcome to L.A., circa 1976 (Box 171)
  - Wild Gold, 1934-02-01 (Box 170)
  - The Wistful Widow of Wagon Gap, circa 1947 (Box 171)
    Contains a screen story outline.
  - You Can't Win 'Em All, 1968-07-11 (Box 171)
- January 2016 Acquisitions, 1942-01-28-1984-04-23; 2.42; (3 boxes)
  - The Adventures of Kit Carson, circa 1952 (Box 176)
    Television script for episode "Mojave Desperados," written by Barry Shipman.
  - Alaska Patrol, circa 1949 (Box 175)
  - The Big Show, 1960-10-05 (Box 175)
  - Boom Town Bad Men, 1949 (Box 175)
    Working title for 1949 film "Roaring Westward."
  - Cisco Kid, 1952-03-24 (Box 176)
    Television script for episode "Canyon City Kid," written by Warren Wilson.
  - Cisco Kid, 1954-04-15 (Box 176)
    Television script for episode "The Caution of Curley Thompson," written by Barry Cohen. Script belonging to actor Marshall Feed, with his name on the front wrapper.
  - City of Bad Men, 1952-10-09 (Box 175)
    Under working title "Gunsmoke."
  - The Constant Nymph, 1942-01-28 (Box 175)
  - Corky, 1970-06-05 (Box 175)
    Under working title "Going."
  - The Dalton Gang, circa 1949 (Box 175)
  - The Devil's Deputy, circa 1947 (Box 175)
    Working title for 1947 film "Trailing Danger."
  - Draw When You're Ready, 1946-08-08 (Box 175)
  - Johnny Ringo, 1959-08-19 (Box 176)
    Television script for episode "The Assassins," written by Teddi Sherman.
  - Jungle Heat, 1956-10-06 (Box 174)
  - Gates of Galilee, 1964-05-12 (Box 175)
  - How the West Was Won, 1976-08-23; (3 folders) (Box 176)
    Script for episode 1 of a television miniseries. Contains several shooting schedules.
  - Land of the Lawless, circa 1947 (Box 175)
  - Laramie, 1963-01-08 (Box 176)
    Television script for episode "The Violent Ones."
  - Lawman, 1962-01-18 (Box 176)
    Television script for episode "The Wanted Man."
  - Lawman, 1961-10-03 (Box 176)
    Television script for episode "Dark Image."
  - Lawman, 1961-11-15 (Box 176)
    Television script for episode "Clooty Hutter."
  - Mexican Silver, 1947 (Box 175)
    Working title for 1950 film "Silver Raiders." Script belonging to actor Marshall Reed, with his notes and an annotated shooting schedule.
  - My Cousin Rachel, 1952-04-28 (Box 175)
  - Range Rider, 1951 (Box 176)
    Television script for episode "Pack Rat," written by Samuel Newman.
  - Red Headed Stranger, 1984-04-23 (Box 175)
    Script contains a costume list, scene breakdowns, and photographs.
  - The Secret Six, 1930-10-06 (Box 175)
  - Sheriff of Cochise, 1956-12-14 (Box 176)
    Television script for episode "Copper Wire."
  - Song of the Saddle, 1947-03-07 (Box 175)
    Working title for 1947 film "Song of the Saddle." Script belonging to actor Marshall Reed, with his notations.
  - The Towering Inferno, 1974-05-06 (Box 174)
  - The Virginian, circa 1970 (Box 176)
    Television script for episode "Tate, Ramrod," written by Arthur Browne, Jr. Seen here as "The Men from Shiloh: Tate: Ramrod."
  - Youngblood Hawke, 1963-02-15 (Box 175)
- September 2016 Acquisition, 1935-01-26-2003-12-05; 4.33; (4 boxes)
  - Anchorman: The Legend of Ron Burgundy, 2003-07-15 (Box 177)
  - Baby Boy, 2000-11-03 (Box 177)
  - Best Friends, circa 1981 (Box 177)
  - Beverly Hills Cop, 1984-04-30 (Box 177)
  - Blacula, 1971-09-01 (Box 177)
  - The Boy from Oklahoma, circa 1953 (Box 177)
  - Brokeback Mountain, 2003-12-05 (Box 177)